A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Henry Carter Stuart, 1874-1918 (bulk 1914-1917)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Executive Papers of Governor Henry Carter Stuart, 1874-1918 (bulk 1914-1917)
The Library of Virginia
28722
32.70 cubic feet and 72 boxes
Virginia. Governor (1914-1918: Stuart)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Governor's Office on 06/30/1975.
Biographical Information
Henry Carter Stuart, of Russell County, served as Governor from 1 February 1914 to 1 February 1918.
Scope and Content
The Executive Papers of Henry Carter Stuart are housed in seventy-two archival boxes and are arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Executive Papers of Governor Henry Carter Stuart, 1874-1918 (bulk 1914-1917)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Separated Material
Oversized items have been separated to Boxes 70-72.
Contents List
- Executive Papers of Governor Henry Carter Stuart, 1874-1918 (bulk 1914-1917)., Extent: 32.70 cubic feet (72 boxes).
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Absent Letters
    - 1914 Mar.-Sept. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1914 Oct.-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1915 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1916 Mar.-Aug. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1916 Sept.-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1917 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Accounting, 1914-1917. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Acknowledgements
    - 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1916-1918 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Adjutant General
    - Correspondence, 1913-1917 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Recommendations
      - Bowles, Maj. Edgar W., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Ellis, Maj. William M., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Sale, Gen. W.W.
        - 1913 Apr.-Nov. (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - 1913 Dec.-1914 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Wortham, Maj. T.M.
        - 1913 July-Sept. (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - 1913 Oct.-1914 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Aeronautics, 1916-1917. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Agricultural Development, 1913-1917. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alexandria Celebration (Washington's Birthday), 1914. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Allen Cases, 1912-1914. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - American Red Cross, 1917-1918. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Anonymous Letters, 1914-1917. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1916-1917. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Appeals for Financial Aid
    - 1914-1916 May (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 1916 June-1917 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Applications for Appointments
    - 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 1915 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 1916 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 1917 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Appointments, 1913-1918. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Appropriations, 1917. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration, 1914-1916. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Armor Plate Plant, 1916-1917. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Art Commission, 1916-1917. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Attorney General, 1916-1918. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Attorney General's Opinions, 1914-1917. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1914-1917. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Autograph Requests, 1914-1917. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Autographs of Governors & Other State Officers, 1915-1917. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bank Deposit Tax, 1914. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Belgian Relief Fund
    - 1914 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 1915-1917 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bills, 1909-1916. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bills, Approval of, 1914-1916. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bills (Unprinted), undated. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Blues (Richmond Light Infantry) Court Martial, 1914. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Boiler Code, 1916-1917. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bonds, 1857-1918. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bonds - De Gonzalez, Juan, 1916. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scouts, 1914-1917. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bryan, William Jennings, 1914. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Buchanan Land Matter, 1914. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Buena Vista Judgeship, 1916. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Bureau of Insurance, 1914-1917. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Campbell's Successor (Judge J. Lawrence Campbell - 30th Judicial Circuit)
    - 1914 Apr. 25-May 8 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 1914 May 9-Sept. 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Square, 1915-1917. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Catawba Sanitarium, 1914-1917. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Central State Hospital, 1915-1918. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Children's Home Society, 1914-1918. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Chiropractor Bill (Senate Bill No. 144), 1912-1914. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - City Government, 1914-1915. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Code Revision
    - 1914 Feb.-June 23 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - 1914 June 24-1916 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Colored Industrial, 1914-1915. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Commission Merchants, 1914-1915. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Uniform Laws, 1914-1917. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Commissioner of Deeds, 1914-1917. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Commissioner of State Hospitals, 1914-1917. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Commissions, 1914-1917. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of the, 1915-1917. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Commutations, 1916-1917. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Confederate Military Records, 1914-1917. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Confederate Reunion
    - 1915-1916 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 1917 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Congratulations
    - 1914 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 1915 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Contingent Fund
    - 1914-1915 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1916-1917 Sept. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 1917 Oct.-1918 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Co-operative Education Association, 1914-1917. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Coordinate College, 1914-1916. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cotton Situation, 1914. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dairy & Food, 1914-1917. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Dairy & Food Commissioner
    - 1914 Mar.-May 11 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 1914 May 12-June (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 1914 July-Aug. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Danville Trip, 1915. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Deaf & Blind School, Colored (Newport News, Va.), 1916. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Deaf, Dumb, & Blind School (Staunton, Va.), 1913-1917. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Delegates Appointed
    - 1914 Feb.-April (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 1914 May-Sept. 14 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 1914 Sept. 15-Dec. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 1915 Jan.-March (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 1915 April-May (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 1915 June-July (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 1915 Aug.-Oct. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 1915 Nov.-Dec. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 1916 Jan.-April (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 1916 May-Sept. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 1916 Oct.-Dec. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 1917 Jan.-Sept. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 1917 Oct.-Dec. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - 1918 Jan. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1915-1916. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Depositories, 1914-1917. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Detectives, 1914-1915. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Dogs, 1916. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Drainage, 1914-1915. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Eastern State Hospital, 1914-1915. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Earhart, W.C., 1914-1915. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Elections (Presidential), 1916. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Engagements
    - 1914 Feb.-June (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - 1914 July-Dec. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - 1915 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 1916 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 1917 Jan.-Aug. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 1917 Sept.-1918 Jan. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Entertainment of Public Men, 1914-1917. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits (State Buildings in Washington), 1916. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Federal Affairs
    - 1914 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 1915 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 1916 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1917 Jan.-June (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 1917 July-1918 Jan. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Federal Legislation, 1914-1917. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Federal Pardons (Capt. Roy Smith), 1914. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Federal Road Appropriation, 1916. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Fee System, 1914-1917. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Fines, Remission of, 1914-1917. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Fish
    - 1913-1914 March (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 1914 April-Oct. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 1915 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1916 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 1917 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of
    - Bowdoin, J. W., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Dudley, S.J., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Duke, C.J., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Eggleston, J.W., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Lee, McDonald, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Lewis, J.M., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Parsons, John M., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Quinby, L.D.T., 1913 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Fisheries, Secretary of
    - Burke, J.J., 1913-1914 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Dodson, W.P., 1913-1914 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Farinhait, T.J., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Howle, W.E., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Lewis, F.W., 1913-1914 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Tabb. J.N., 1913 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Taylor, S.A., 1913-1914 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Flags
    - 1914-1915 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Foodstuffs, High Cost of, 1916-1917 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1914-1918 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Forester, State, 1917-1918 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Forestry
    - 1913-1914 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 1915 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 1916 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 1917 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Gaines, Grenville (Adjutant General), 1913 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Game
    - 1914-1915 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 1916 Jan.-April (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Geological Survey
    - 1914 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 1915 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 1916 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 1917 Jan.-Aug. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 1917 Sept.-Dec. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 1918 Jan. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - German War, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Gettysburg Monument, 1916-1917 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Gettysburg Monument - Dedication Program, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Gifts, 1914-1917 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Goetze Case, 1915 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Government Plant for Manufacturing Armor Plate, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Conference
    - 1914-1915 Aug. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 1915 Sept.-1916 Sept. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - 1916 Oct.-1917 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Greetings, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Grounds and Buildings, 1914-1918 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Hampton Normal & Agricultural Institute, 1914-1917 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commissioner, 1913 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Hodges, LeRoy, 1914-1917 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Hodges, W.T., 1914 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Honorary Memberships
    - 1913-1914 April (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - 1914 May-1915 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - 1917 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Hopewell
    - 1915 July-Sept. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - 1915 Oct.-Nov. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - 1915 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - 1916 Jan.-June (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 1916 July-1918 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Hopewell Appointments, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Horticultural Society, 1915 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Hospitals, Commissioner of
    - 1913 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 1914 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 1915 Jan. 2-9 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 1915 Jan. 11-30 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - 1915 Feb.-Aug. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Houdon Statue of George Washington, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - House of Southern Governors, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Immigration
    - 1913-1914 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 1915 Jan.-Aug. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 1915 Sept.-1916 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Inauguration, 1913-1917 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Indian Affairs, 1914-1917 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Industrial Home School for Wayward Colored Girls, 1914-1917 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Inebriates, 1914-1917 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Insane
    - 1914-1915 June (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 1915 July-1916 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 1917 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Invitations Extended
    - 1914-1915 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 1916 Feb.-Sept. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - 1916 Oct.-Dec. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - 1917 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Invitations - Social
    - 1914-1915 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - 1916 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Invitations - Speaking
    - 1913-1914 March (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - 1914 April-May (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - 1914 June-July (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - 1914 Aug.-Sept. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - 1914 Oct. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - 1914 Nov.-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - 1915 Jan.-March (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - 1915 April (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - 1915 May (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - 1915 June-July (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - 1915 Aug. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - 1915 Sept. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - 1915 Oct.-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - 1916 Jan.-March (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - 1916 Apr.-May (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - 1916 June-Sept. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - 1916 Oct.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - 1917 Jan.-June (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - 1917 July-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - 1917 Oct.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Irrigation, 1914-1915 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Jackson (Stonewall) Monument, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Jamestown Exposition (Sale of Virginia Building), 1917 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Johnston Monument (Vicksburg Battlefield), 1915 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Judges
    - Appointment of, 1914-1917 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Designation of
      - 1914 Feb.-May (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - 1914 June-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - 1914 Oct.-Dec. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - 1915 Jan.-May (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - 1915 June-Oct. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - 1915 Nov.-Dec. (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - 1916 Jan.-May (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - 1916 June-Oct. (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - 1916 Nov.-Dec. (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - 1917 Jan.-June (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - 1917 July-Dec. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Judgeship
    - Circuit Court, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Roanoke, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Seventeenth Circuit
      - 1916 July-Sept. 1914 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - 1916 Oct.-Dec. 1914 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Supreme Court of Appeals
      - 1915-1916 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - 1917 Jan.-Feb. 17 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - 1917 Feb. 19-21 1914 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - 1917 Feb. 22-24 1914 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - 1917 Feb. 26-Mar. 19 1914 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Turner, Edward S. (Twenty-Sixth Judicial Circuit)
      - 1916 Dec. 1-7 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - 1916 Dec. 8-30 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Supreme Court, 1916 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Judicial Procedure, 1914-1917 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Keller, Judge Joseph L. (Successor to) (Bristol Corporation Court), 1914 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Kings Mountain Celebration, 1915-1916 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Labor Commissioner
    - 1913-1917 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Colvin, Howard T., 1915 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Pace, M. R., 1915 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Laurel Industrial School, 1914-1917 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Lee Camp Soldiers' Home, 1910-1917 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Lee, W. McDonald, 1913-1914 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Reference Bureau, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Legum (Israel) Extradition, 1916-1917 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Letters - Introductory, 1914-1918 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Lime Grinding Board
    - 1914 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 1915 Jan.-July (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 1915 Aug. 2-10 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 1915 Aug. 11-24 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 1915 Aug. 25-Sept. 13 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - 1915 Sept. 15-Oct. 30 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - 1915 Nov.-Dec. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - 1916 Jan.-Feb. 10 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 1916 Feb. 11-29 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - 1916 Mar.-July (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - 1916 Aug.-Sept. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Lincoln Memorials, 1914-1917 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Lynching, 1917 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Mansion, 1915-1917 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Medical College of Virginia, 1914-1917 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Merchant Marine, 1914-1917 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Messages of State Governors
    - 1914-1916 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 1917 Jan. 2-16 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 1917 Jan. 20-Apr. 16 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 1917-Undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Military
    - 1910-1914 July (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 1914 Aug.-Dec. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 1915 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - 1916 Jan.-May (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - 1916 June (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - 1916 July 1-19 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - 1916 July 22-Aug. 15 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - 1916 Aug. 16-31 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - 1916 Sept. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - 1916 Oct. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - 1916 Nov.-Dec. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - 1917 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1914 Jan.-March (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 1914 April-May (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - 1914 June-July (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - 1914 Aug.-Sept. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - 1914 Oct. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - 1914 Nov.-Dec. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - 1915 Jan.-Feb. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - 1915 March-May (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - 1915 June-July (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - 1915 Aug.-Sept. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - 1915 Oct.-Nov. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - 1915 Dec. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - 1916 Jan.-Feb. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - 1916 March 1-20 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - 1916 March 21-31 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - 1916 April (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - 1916 May-June (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Monticello, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Morgan (Thomas) Case, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Mount Vernon, 1914-1917 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - National Agricultural Society, 1916-1917 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - National Democratic Campaign, 1916-1917 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - National Security, 1915-1916 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Negro Affairs, 1916-1917 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Negro Reformatory (Hanover County), 1916 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Interviews
    - 1913-1914 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - 1915-1916 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Norfolk Racetrack, 1914-1915 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Notaries Public
    - 1914 Jan.-June (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - 1914 July-Dec. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - 1915 Jan.-May (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - 1915 June-Dec. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - 1916 Jan.-June (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - 1916 July-Dec. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - 1917 Jan.-June (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - 1917 July-Dec. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - 1918 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Office Supplies, 1914-1917 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Offices in Capital, 1914-1915 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Officials in Other States, 1914 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Optometry, 1914-1917 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Orders to Print, 1914-1918 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Organizations
    - 1913-1914 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 1915 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - 1916 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Ouster Law, 1916 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Panama-Pacific Exposition
    - 1904-1914 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - 1915-1916 May (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - 1916 June-1917 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Applications for Employment, 1914-1915 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Architects, 1914-1915 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Bills & Receipts, 1914-1915 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Commissioners
      - 1914 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - 1915 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Contractors, 1914-1915 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Decorations, Models, Buttons, Badges, & Souvenirs 1914 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Exhibits, 1914-1915 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Expenses, 1915-1916 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Hostess, 1914-1915 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Houdon Statue, 1914 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1914-1915 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Mount Vernon (Virginia State Building)
      - 1914 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - 1915 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Moving Pictures, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Railroads Exhibit (Agricultureal, Horticultural, & Mineral), 1914-1915 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Statements & Receipts
      - 1915 Feb.-July (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - 1915 Aug.-1916 Jan. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Trip, 1914-1915 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Day
      - 1914-1915 June (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - 1915 July-Aug. (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - 1915 Sept.-Nov. (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Vouchers
      - No. 1-50, 1914 June-Dec. (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - No. 51-100, 1914 Dec.-1915 May (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - No. 101-125, 1915 May-Nov. (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - No. 126-148, 1915 Nov.-1916 Feb. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Pardons
    - 1914 Feb.-May (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - 1914 June-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - 1914 Sept.-Nov. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - 1914 Dec. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - 1915 Jan.-Mar. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - 1915 Apr.-June (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - 1915 July-Sept. 15 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - 1915 Sept. 16-Nov. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - 1915 Dec. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - 1916 Jan.-May (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - 1916 June-Sept. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - 1916 Oct.-Dec. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - 1917 Jan.-April (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - 1917 May-June (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - 1917 July-Sept. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - 1917 Oct.-Dec. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - 1918 Jan. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - List of Conditional Pardons, 1914-1916 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Paroles
    - 1914-1917 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Convicts for Road Work, 1916-1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Penitentiary, 1915-1917 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Penitentiary Board
    - 1914-1916 Oct. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - 1916 Nov.-1917 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Penology, 1914-1917 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Pensions
    - 1914 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - 1915-1916 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - 1917 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Permits, 1914-1915 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Perry Celebration, 1914 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Pharmacy Board, 1914 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Phoebus Gambling Investigation, 1917 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Photograph Requests, 1914-1917 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Political Disabilities, 1914-1918 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Preparedness, 1914-1917 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Primaries, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Prison Labor, 1914-1917 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Proclamations
    - 1907-1914 Nov. 10 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - 1914 Nov. 11-Dec. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - 1915 Jan.-July (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - 1915 Aug.-Dec. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - 1916 Jan.-Nov. 23 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - 1916 Nov. 24-Dec. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - 1917 Jan.-Aug. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - 1917 Sept.-Dec. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Produce Exchange, 1914. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Progressive Democratic League, 1914. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Prohibition Commissioner
    - 1916-1917 June (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - 1917 July-1918 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Projected Railways, 1916 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Legislation
    - 1914-1915 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Public Pinting, 1914-1917. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Quarantine
    - 1914 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - 1915 Jan.-March 5 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - 1915 March 10-31 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - 1915 April-May (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - 1915 June-Dec. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - 1916 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Quarantine Officer, 1914-1916 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Rabies, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Rats, 1909-1915 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Rats, 1914-1917 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Reciprocal Automoblie Arrangements with Foreign Countries, 1916 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Recommendations
    - 1916 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - 1917 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Referred to Departments, 1914-1917 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Referred to Local Officials
    - 1914 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - 1915 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Referred to Organizations, 1915 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Register of the Land Office, 1914 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Reports, 1914-1917 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Requests for Contributions
    - 1913-1916 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - 1917 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Requests for Information
    - 1916 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - 1917 Jan.-April (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 1917 May-July (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - 1917 Aug.-Dec. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 1918 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Requests for Publications
    - 1914 Jan.-Oct. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 1914 Nov.-Dec. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - 1915 Jan.-May (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - 1915 June-Oct. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - 1915 Nov.-Dec. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 1916 Jan.-May (Box 54, Folder 2)